export const htmlQuestions = [
    {
        "Question": "HTML is the standard ____ language for creating Web pages?",
        "option1": "scripting",
        "option2": "programming",
        "option3": "styling",
        "answer": "markup"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML stands for_______?",
        "option1": "Hyperactive Text Markup Language",
        "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "option2": "Hyper Text Machine Language",
        "option3": "None of these"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is the correct syntax to include comment in an HTML document?",
        "option1": "//",
        "option2": "/* Comment */",
        "option3": "// Comment //",
        "answer": "<!-- Comment -->"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Can we hide content using the comment?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Can we hide inline content using the comment?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which element/tag defines a paragraph?",
        "answer": "<p>",
        "option1": "<pre>",
        "option2": "<panel>",
        "option3": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag/element defines the HTML document's body?",
        "option1": "<HTML>",
        "option2": "<HTMLbody>",
        "option3": "<bdy>",
        "answer": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag contains the meta information about the HTML page?",
        "option1": "<html>",
        "option2": "<title>",
        "answer": "<head>",
        "option3": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is the root element of an HTML page?",
        "answer": "<html>",
        "option1": "<title>",
        "option2": "<head>",
        "option3": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who invented HTML?",
        "option1": "Dave Raggett",
        "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "option2": "Denis Ritchie",
        "option3": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML tags with no content are called _____?",
        "option1": "Special tags",
        "option2": "Advanced tags",
        "answer": "Empty tags",
        "option3": "Other tags"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Nested HTML Elements are allowed in HTML?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is HTML a case sensitive?",
        "option1": "Yes",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML headings are defined with the _____ tags?",
        "option1": "<head1> to <head6>",
        "option2": "<p1> to <p6>",
        "answer": "<h1> to <h6>",
        "option3": "<h1> to <h3>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to display a horizontal rule (horizotnal line)?",
        "option1": "<br>",
        "answer": "<hr>",
        "option2": "<hr>...</hr>",
        "option3": "<line>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct syntax of <hr> tag?",
        "option1": "<hr>",
        "option2": "<hr />",
        "option3": "None of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to define a line break?",
        "option1": "<\\n>",
        "option2": "<lr>",
        "answer": "<br>",
        "option3": "<br>...</br>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct syntax of <br> tag?",
        "option1": "<br>",
        "option2": "<br />",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "option3": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to define preformatted text?",
        "option1": "<pf>",
        "option2": "<p>",
        "answer": "<pre>",
        "option3": "<code>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which HTML attribute is used to define styles of an element?",
        "option1": "<style>",
        "option2": "<css>",
        "answer": "style",
        "option3": "css"
    }
];